[door opens]
-[Caine]: Bubble, thank God you're here!
I forgot to make a trailer
for the next episode
of "The Amazing Digital Circus,"
and my flight to Copper 9
leaves in five minutes!
I need you to handle this one
for me, buddy!
[door slams]
-[Bubble]: [overlapping vocalizing]
[DOINK!]
Coming to a theater nearby,
the next episode
of "The Great Gasicals District"--
episode of the "Ungreat Amazing Circus"
is coming now.
-[Ragatha]:
The gang finded themselfies
faced with a challeng.
"Challenge"?
[stammers]
They gois in the hole
and throweth lifesavers
down a tumor seal --
What?
What is this?
-[Bubble]:
Prepare for 101 views.
-[Jax]: The green man
writing a cringey musicalely
about Regada
in only threely days.
-[Bubble]: [stammers]
101 laughs.
-[Ragatha]: Uh, wait --
What did he say about me?
-[Jax]: What, you think I can make
any sense out of this garbage?
-[Bubble]:
101 frightens.
-[Ragatha]: [sighs]
I-I dunno.
Sometimes there's logic
in his nonsense.
-[Bubble]: The motion picture
that's ever created.
[stammers]
-[female voice]: AudioJungle.
-[Ragatha]: Uh, well...
Stay tuned for the episode?
I guess?
-[Jax]: That was awful.
-[Episode 3 narrator]:
Does anyone have bus fare?
I -- I want to go home
to my wife
and kids now, please.